{
    "q1": {
        "id": "q1",
        "question": "The oldest Known mattress dates back...",
        "answers": [
            "800 Years",
            "6,500,000 Years",
            "77,000 Years",
            "13,500 Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "77,000 Years"
    },

    "q2": {
        "id": "q2",
        "question": "The invention of the raised bed is credited to...",
        "answers": [
            "The Ancient Egyptians",
            "The Romans",
            "The Incans",
            "The Tang Dynasty"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The Ancient Egyptians"
    },

    "q3": {
        "id": "q3",
        "question": "Which type of bed was invented first?",
        "answers": [
            "Murphy Bed",
            "Air Mattress",
            "Water Bed",
            "Futon Sofa Bed"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Air Mattress"
    },

    "q4": {
        "id": "q4",
        "question": "Which country boasts having the worlds oldest door?",
        "answers": [
            "Switzerland",
            "Turkey",
            "Tibet",
            "Argentina"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Switzerland"
    },

    "q5": {
        "id": "q5",
        "question": "What year was the first flush toilet invented?",
        "answers": [
            "1818",
            "430",
            "184 BC",
            "1596"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1596"
    },

    "q6": {
        "id": "q6",
        "question": "How did the Romans wipe their bum? (these all were worldly realities)",
        "answers": [
            "Tersorium - A sponge on a stick",
            "Ostraca - broken pieces of ceremic pottery, smoothed around the edges",
            "Hand (and then wash said hand)",
            "Corn cobs, yep, corn. cobs."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Tersorium - A sponge on a stick"
    },

    "q7": {
        "id": "q7",
        "question": "Which of these were used for windows in England before glass took over?",
        "answers": [
            "Plant Weaves",
            "Tin",
            "Animal Horns",
            "Sand"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Animal Horns"
    },

    "q8": {
        "id": "q8",
        "question": "Which utensil was considered to be blasphemous and an offense to God?",
        "answers": [
            "Forks",
            "Mortar and Pestles",
            "Slotted Spoons",
            "Waffle Irons"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Forks"
    },

    "q9": {
        "id": "q9",
        "question": "Which playground game was an Olympic sport?",
        "answers": [
            "Four Square",
            "Capture the Flag",
            "Red Rover",
            "Tug of War"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Tug of War"
    },

    "q10": {
        "id": "q10",
        "question": "Which royal of England had knighted men, known as Grooms of Stool, to wipe their bum after using the loo",
        "answers": [
            "Prince Harry",
            "King Henry VIII",
            "Queen Elizabeth II",
            "Queen Victoria"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "King Henry VIII"
    }

}